{
    "results": [
      {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Name the first women who cross the English Channel?",
        "correct_answer": "Arti Gupta",
        "incorrect_answers1": "Sneh Singh",
        "incorrect_answers2": "Ujwala Rai",
        "incorrect_answers3": "None of the above"
      },
      {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Youngest woman to climb Mount Everest two times in India?",
        "correct_answer": "Dicky Dolma",
        "incorrect_answers1": "Omana",
        "incorrect_answers2": "Faria",
        "incorrect_answers3": "None of the above"
        
      },
      {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "First woman to pass MA in India?",
        "correct_answer": "Chandra Mukhi Bose",
        "incorrect_answers1": "Leila Seth",
        "incorrect_answers2": "Kadambani Bose",
        "incorrect_answers3": "Thresia"
        
      },
      {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Name the first woman who become doctor on India? ",
        "correct_answer": "Kadambani Ganguli",
        "incorrect_answers1": "Cornelia Sorabji",
        "incorrect_answers2": "Ujwala Rai",
        "incorrect_answers3": "Anita Bose"
      },
      {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "First woman to circumnavigate around the world?",
        "correct_answer": "Ujwala Rai",
        "incorrect_answers1": "Anna George",
        "incorrect_answers2": "Sucheta Kriplani",
        "incorrect_answers3": "None of the above"
      },
      {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "First woman who recieved a Sena Medal in India",
        "correct_answer": "Bimla Devi",
        "incorrect_answers1": "Dicky Dolma",
        "incorrect_answers2": "Santosh Yadav",
        "incorrect_answers3": "Kiran Devi"
      },
      {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Name the first woman who become the speaker of Lok Sabha in India ?",
        "correct_answer": "Mrs Shanno Devi",
        "incorrect_answers1": "Leila Seth",
        "incorrect_answers2": "Reita Feria",
        "incorrect_answers3": "Mrs Sarojini Naidu"
      },
      {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "First woman editor of English newspaper in India ?",
        "correct_answer": "Dina Vakil",
        "incorrect_answers1": "P.K Thresia",
        "incorrect_answers2": "Anna Chandi",
        "incorrect_answers3": "None of the above"

      },
      {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "Name the first woman who become the advocate in India?",
        "correct_answer": "Cornelia Sarabji",
        "incorrect_answers1": "Arti Shah",
        "incorrect_answers2": "Kamla Devi",
        "incorrect_answers3": "None of the above"

      },
      {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "The woman who become the first IAS officer in India?",
        "correct_answer": "Anna George Malhotra",
        "incorrect_answers1": "M. Fatima Biwi",
        "incorrect_answers2": "Kiran Bedi",
        "incorrect_answers3": "None of the above"
      },
      {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "Who is the first Indian women to win  the WTA title?",
        "correct_answer": "Sania Mirza",
        "incorrect_answers1": "Shaina Nehwal",
        "incorrect_answers2": "Mary Kom",
        "incorrect_answers3": "Matina Hingis"

      },
      {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Who is the first women to fly among space?",
        "correct_answer": " Valentina Terreshkova",
        "incorrect_answers1": "Kalpana Chawla",
        "incorrect_answers2": "Shunita Williams",
        "incorrect_answers3": "Shanon Lucid"
      }
    ]
}